李医生  请到4142病房
Dr. Lee, call 4142.
李医生  4142病房
Dr. Lee, 4142.
还要等很久吗
Will it, uh, be much longer?
准备好了我们就叫你
We'll call you when we're ready.
我都等了快一个小时了
I've been waiting almost an hour.
准备好了我们就叫你
We'll call you when we're ready.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
那么  她真要回来了吗
So she's really coming back?
谁要回来
Who's coming back?
你不认识
You don't know her.
你给她加薪  还是增加福利
You give her a raise? Increase her benefits?
我们可没有数码录放机
Don't have TiVo on this thing.
不能回放  闭嘴
Can't rewind. Shut up.
减少她的工作时间吗
You lower her hours?
你都不认识她
You don't even know her.
-这家伙是谁  -是个病人
- Who is this guy? - He's a patient.
他在给我做检查
He's examining me.
检查一结束  他就得回去工作
He's gotta go back to work as soon as I'm done with the examination.
估计我也是
Guess I do too.
一定有什么缘故
It's gotta be something.
她应该不是因为喜欢你才回来的
She didn't come back because she likes you.
等等
Wait a minute.
她就是因为喜欢你才回来的
She did come back because she likes you.
你这家伙  你和她上床了
You dog. You slept with her.
你再说  我就给你做前列腺检查
Keep talking. I'll finish your exam with a prostate check.
我答应和她约会一次
I've agreed to take her on one date.
-什么  -那么你喜欢她吗
- What? - So, you into this girl?
是
Yes.
不  我  我没的选
No. She-- She's not giving me any choice.
慢着  她逼你和她上床吗
Wait. She's making you do her?
是和她约会
Date her.
年轻单纯的医生爱上年长粗鲁的导师
Young ingenue doctor falling in love with gruff, older mentor--
她的甜蜜温柔让他愿意揭开旧伤疤
Her sweet, gentle nature bringing him to a closer,
再次面对自己曾经受伤的心
Fuller understanding of his wounded heart.
上了她吧
Do her...
不然你就是同志
or you're gay.
老天
For God's sakes.
*相依树中  甜蜜吻拥*
*Sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G*
成熟点吧  好好练练你们的和声
Grow up. And learn to harmonize.
-该死  -抱歉  抱歉
- Damn it! - I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
谁带着个没盖的尿液样本到处转啊
Who the hell walks around with an open urine sample?
对不起  我没  没
I'm sorry. I didn't-- I didn't--
你有点反应过度了吧
You think that was a bit of an overreaction?
他把尿弄我身上了
Well, he peed on me.
难道还要我高兴不成
I'm not into that.
是苹果汁
It's apple juice.
现在去找那个家伙  向他道歉
Now go find that guy and apologize.
再有一个病人投诉  你就要停职检查了
One more patient complaint and you're looking at a suspension.
我原谅你毁了我的外套
I forgive you for ruining my jacket.
听着  你看着像是个正常人
Look, you seem like a regular kind of guy--
不是那种会给另一个正常人找麻烦的
not the type to get another regular guy into trouble.
我说得对吗
Am I right?
给你20块  不要哭了
Twenty bucks cash if you'll stop crying.
原谅我吧  骂我吧
Forgive me. Yell at me.
给我些回应  好吗
Just give me something I can work with, okay?
比赛结束了
Game's over.
-你们两个和好了吗  -找个轮椅来
- You two make nice? - Get a wheelchair.
-送这个家伙去急诊室  -怎么了
- Get this guy into the E.R. - What happened?
-右眼瞳孔扩张  -天
- Right pupil's blown. - Holy--
你把他弄中风了吗
You gave the guy a stroke?
于是狗熊拿兔子来擦屁股
So the bear wipes himself with the rabbit.
不好笑
Lame.
-你在这里干什么  -我在这里工作
- What are you doing here? - I work here.
"这里"是指这里吗  这间办公室
"Here" Here? In this office?
事实上  豪斯求我回来的
House practically begged me to come back.
说吧  你是不是狠狠敲诈了一笔
Please tell me you took him to the cleaners.
薪水还是一样低
Same lousy salary.
那么你为何还要回来
Then why'd you do it?
因为这是世界上最幸福的地方
Because this is the happiest place on Earth.
21岁男性  因磨牙就诊
Twenty-one-year-old male-- Comes in with grinding of the teeth.
然后豪斯让他中风了  瞳孔完全放大
And House gives him a stroke. Totally blew out his pupil.
你把一个家伙给吓得中风了吗
You scared a guy into stroking out?
这里有人感到惊讶吗
Does that surprise anyone here?
瞳孔放大通常意味着脑干水肿
Blown pupils usually means brain stem edema.
没错  不过既然他没死也没昏迷
Sure, but since he's not dead or in a coma,
我认为是视神经区域中风
I'm going with stroke to the optic nerve.
断层扫描显示两件事
C.T. Scan shows two things.
局部缺血  脑组织死亡
Ischemia-- death of brain tissue.
意味着有损伤  还好不是永久性的
Means there's been some damage, hopefully not permanent.
-还有呢  -没了
- And? - And that's it.
单从X光片上看不出具体病因
There's nothing there to tell us what the underlying cause is.
得做核磁共振
Gotta do an M.R.I.
你看的地方不对
You're looking at the wrong part of the scan.
我在看大脑  还有什么
I'm looking at the brain. What else is there?
下颌
The jaw.
下颌告诉我们中风的原因吗
The jaw tells us why he stroked?
不  下颌告诉我们不能做核磁共振的原因
No, the jaw tells us why we can't do an M.R.I.
除非我们想要他的下巴飞出来
Unless we want his jawbone flying across the room.
金属板  他做过大型面部重塑手术
Metal plate. He's had major reconstruction,
我们没法取出它
And there's no way we're removing it,
所以我们必须更聪明点
So we're forced to be clever.
做血管造影以排除血管炎
Angiogram to rule out vasculitis,
做肌电图检查外周神经损伤
E.M.G. for peripheral neuropathy,
做毒理检测毒品
Tox screen to eliminate drugs,
超声检查以排除心脏栓塞
And echo to rule out cardiac emboli.
卡梅隆医生
Dr. Cameron,
若你能保守新合同条约不外泄
I'd appreciate you keeping
我将非常感激
the terms of your new contract to yourself.
别让其他人也来要同样的额外福利
Don't want everyone clamoring for the same perks.
-什么额外福利  -你们不会感兴趣的
- What perks? - Nothing you'd be interested in.
那么就不是钱
So it's not money, then?
办公室吗  保险  停车位
Office space, insurance, parking--
任何他能给你的  我们都感兴趣
Anything he could offer you, we'd be interested in.
他答应和我约会一次
He agreed to go on a date with me.
约会吗
A date?
约会  晚餐  看电影
Date, dinner and a movie,
脱光光  大汗淋漓那种约会吗
Naked and sweaty, date?
他就同意前面两项
He only committed to the first two.
他太  太老了
He's so-- He's so old.
-而你  太年轻了  -是个重大错误
- And you're so young. - It's a big mistake.
他是我的老板
It's my boss.
我可以合法地性骚扰我老板
I'm allowed to sexually harass my boss.
我去安排肌电图  你准备血管造影
I'll arrange for the E.M.G. You will set up the angiogram.
而你去取血液样本
And you can get the blood samples,
问病史  得到病人知情同意书
Patient history, patient consent.
就像明知会发生一场事故  却只能坐视
Like watching an accident about to happen.
早上好
Morning.
哈维  我是福曼医生
Harvey, I'm Dr. Foreman.
来询问你的病情
I'm here to discuss your case.
我是安妮特  哈维的朋友
I'm Annette. I'm Harvey's friend.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
我需要你的近亲信息
I need your next of kin.
入院表上  你没有填写
You didn't fill that out on your intake form.
哈维的父母去世了
Harvey's parents are dead.
死于两年前的车祸
They died two years ago in a car crash.
知道了
I see.
那么哈维  你有兄弟姐妹吗
So, Harvey, you have any siblings?
没有  没有祖父母
No. And no grandparents,
也没有叔叔阿姨
Or uncles or aunts.
安妮特  我不想让你离开
Annette, uh, I don't want to have to ask you to leave--
我要她留下
I want her to stay.
她可以留下  但是你来回答问题
Well, she can stay. You do the talking.
你今早为何来门诊
Why'd you come to the clinic this morning?
大概6个月前  我开始磨...
Uh, about six months ago, I started grinding my--
就是嘴里面  你用来咀嚼食物的东西
You know. In your mouth. You chew with them.
牙
Teeth.
哈维有点命名性失语症
Harvey's experiencing a little nominal aphasia. Hmm.
记不住名词
You know, when you can't remember nouns.
对  我知道什么是命名性失语症
Yeah, I think I know what nominal aphasia is.
你治疗过磨牙吗
Have you had any treatment for the teeth grinding?
我去了
I went to a--
他们用那个非常尖的东西做那个
You know, they do that thing with the sharp pointy things.
针头吗  采血吗
Needles? Someone took your blood?
不是  他们让你呼吸
No. They make you breathe.
胸肺科医生吗
Pulmonologist?
不是  她用了某种...
No. She had this, uh--
她用了一种电子仪器
She had this electrical machine.
他见了一个针灸师
He saw an acupuncturist.
你知道针灸师做了什么吗
Do you know what the acupuncturist did?
她诊断说是肝气郁结
She diagnosed liver chi stagnation
让哈维去见一个安神师
And sent Harvey to a shen balancer.
他把他转给了个顺势疗法医生
He referred him to a homeopathic doctor,
而他让他去找推拿医师
Who sent him to a chiropractor.
这很正常嘛
Naturally.
推拿医师认为可能是食物过敏
The chiropractor thought it might be food sensitivity
让哈维去见了自然疗法医师
And sent Harvey to a naturopath.
自然疗法医师又把我送回了
The naturopath sent me back to the--
-送回了针灸师  -对
- Back to the acupuncturist. - Yes.
好吧
Okay. Well,
我们需要看所有医生的病历
we'll need to see the records... of all of those, uh, practitioners.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
血管造影都准备好了吗
Everything set for the angiogram?
卡梅隆先做肌电图  那是谁
Cameron's got the E.M.G. first. Who's that?
哈维的古鲁
Harvey's guru.
她自己这么说的吗
That's what she called herself?
她表现得就像那个样子
That's what she acted like.
我阴道疼
Hi. I'm having vaginal pain.
幸会
Pleasure to meet you.
我的妇科医生最近死了  他人很好
My OB/GYN died recently. He was a nice man.
-手很暖  -我的手可不暖
- Warm hands. - Not anymore.
那你小便的时候疼吗
So, does it hurt when you tinkle?
是  疼得更厉害
Yeah, that's when it's worst.
你的阴道撕裂
You have some vaginal tearing.
没有瘀伤
No sign of bruising.
没有外伤和强行进入迹象
No indication of trauma, forced entry.
瑞蒙娜  你这个坏女孩
Ramona, you naughty girl.
你不是找了个18岁的男友
Either you've got yourself an 18-year-old boyfriend,
就是有个80岁男友  他还爱吃蓝色小药丸
or an 80-year-old with some little blue pills.
玛艾隆就想试试
Myron thought he'd just try 'em out.
-你真"性福"  -我想也是
- Lucky you. - I guess.
你是否更愿意玛艾隆萎上那么一点呢
You'd prefer it if Myron was a little...droopier?
或许有点吧
Maybe a little.
我们过去常牵着手  一起看书
We used to hold hands or read together...
看《机智问答》节目
or watch Jeopardy.
我都快一个月没看《机智问答》了
I haven't seen Jeopardy in almost a month.
你和他谈过这个吗
Have you talked to him about this?
你试试说服一个73岁的人放弃性生活
You try talking a 73-year-old out of sex.
有了那些重振雄风的东西
With all these male enhancements,
说服他们放弃是不可能的
the pressure to put out's incredible.
欲望比年轻气盛的时候还要强烈
It's worse than high school.
如果他无法从我身上满足所需的话
He doesn't get what he wants from me,
就会去找街角公寓的康妮偷腥
he'll get it from Connie in the corner condo.
她把头发染成红色  真是个老荡妇
She's dying her hair red. Major league slut.
我给你开个阴道雌激素栓剂的处方
Here's a prescription for vaginal estrogen suppositories.
能帮助润滑
It'll help with the lubrication.
谢谢
Thank you.
或许你能给玛艾隆也开个方子
Maybe you could give Myron a prescription--
用点药性稍微弱点的药
something weaker than he's got now.
只要告诉他这有利于他的心脏  他会相信的
Tell him it's better for his heart. He'd buy that.
你没办法对他说实话  所以要我骗他
You can't tell him the truth so you want me to lie to him?
-可以吗  -把腿并拢
- Would you? - Close your legs.
人的神经系统通过产生微弱电流
Nerves stimulate muscles to move
来刺激肌肉的运动
by creating a small electrical current.
这仪器能检测到这种电流
The machine will measure that.
我会用针刺入不同的肌肉
And I will insert this needle into various muscles
让你做一些屈曲运动
and ask you to flex.
有时候会很痛
Sometimes it can be painful.
-告诉我  我就拔出来  -不
- Let me know. I can pull back. - No
我是说  没关系
I mean, it's okay.
好吧  把你的手伸出来
Okay. Put your arm out to the side.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You all right? - I'm good.
不必停
You don't have to stop.
把手举过头顶
Raise your arm over your head.
肌电图检查没问题
The E.M.G. was clean.
根据诊疗史来看
Based on this history,
可能是顺势疗法医生给他服用了有毒性的草药
it's either toxic herbs from the homeopath,
也可能是中医推拿师造成了脊椎损伤
spinal damage from the chiropractor,
也可能是针灸医师不小心用了
infection from a needle that the acupuncturist
扎过蝾螈眼睛的针头引起的感染
accidentally let sit in eye of newt,
又或者那个安神师
or the shen balancer--
"神"到底是个什么玩意儿
What the hell is a shen,
怎么会不安
and how come it's lopsided?
我们只在超声波检查中发现了异常
The only abnormal test result we found was on the echo report.
二尖瓣脱垂
Mitral valve prolapse.
挂个小招牌
Hang up a shingle
抨击西医的局限性
and condemn the narrowness and greed of Western medicine.
你们就能大发了
You can make a damn fine living.
病变的瓣膜上出现血栓
Clots form on the faulty valve,
血栓脱落造成脑栓塞  因而引起中风
get sent to the brain, voil- stroke.
是啊  反正治不死人
Of course, no harm, no foul.
不过是从迷信的白痴手里赚些钱而已
Just taking a few bucks from superstitious idiots, right?
也可能是由外伤引起的动脉瘤
Could also be an aneurysm due to trauma.
哪里来的外伤  难道是被推拿师弄伤的
Trauma? From what, the chiropractic treatments?
是细菌性心内膜炎  瓣膜感染了
It's bacterial endocarditis, an infected valve.
我们应该做血液培养
We should do blood cultures.
他看了六个月的庸医
The six months that he had with these charlatans...
还不如找个切合实际
might have been better spent going to someone
相信科学的医生呢
who looks at things that exist in the real world.
不过这又是鄙人狭隘的想法
But that's just me being all narrow again.
我给哈维检查时
I noticed a small bruit
发现左侧颈动脉有杂音
when I listened to Harvey's left carotid.
这种杂音很可能是由外伤引起的动脉瘤引起的
You could hear that if he had an aneurysm from trauma.
血管造影能看出是否有动脉瘤
An aneurysm would have shown on the angiogram.
未必  不一定
No. Not necessarily.
左右为难啊
Quite a dilemma.
神奇的水晶球  为我指明方向吧
Oh, great pool-hall oracle, grant me guidance.
我们是该相信福曼
Do we go with Foreman's theory,
那套基于各项医学检测结果而提出的看法呢
which is at least marginally supported by medical test results,
还是该相信奇斯
or Chase's theory,
虽然那是完全没有医学根据的奇思妙想
that is completely unsupported by medical evidence?
请明示
What to do?
不管怎样  那家伙的下巴明显骨折过
The guy obviously broke his jaw somehow.
说不定还有别的什么外伤
Who knows what other trauma he's suffered?
我们应该再做一次血管造影
We should do the angiogram again.
所有的迹象都表明
And all signs point to--
抱歉  奇斯  天神发话了
Ah. Sorry, Chase. The gods have spoken.
给哈维上血液稀释剂和抗生素
Start Harvey on blood thinners and antibiotics.
哇  我明白了  豪斯是多么可爱啊
Wow. Yeah, I get it. House is adorable.
我真想牢牢握住他  永不分离
I just want to hold him and never let go.
天呐  你在干什么呢
My God! What the hell are you doing?
她要掐死他
She's choking him.
福曼  住手  放了她
Foreman, stop. Let her go.
-她刚才想杀了他  -不  她没有
- She was trying to kill him. - No. No, she wasn't.
各项生命体征正常
His vitals seem okay.
拜托  别伤害她
Please-- Please, don't hurt her.
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on in here?
她是  她是"施虐女王"
She's-- She's a dominatrix.
没错吧  安妮特
Right, Annette?
是病人要求你勒住他的吗
The patient asked you to strangle him?
哈维有窒息癖
Harvey is an asphyxiaphyliac.
他喜欢被人掐着  体验窒息的快感
He likes to be strangled or smothered.
真是有病
That's just sick.
这个法律观点倒是有趣
Well, that's an intriguing legal opinion.
哎呀  这算哪门子的律师啊
Geez. What kind of a lawyer is he?
你要专业的法律意见吗  报警
You want a legal opinion? Call the cops.
我很小心
I was careful.
我一直注意着监护仪
I watched the monitors. Made sure
保证他的血氧量大于90
his O2 sats were over 90.
我不会伤害他
I would never hurt him.
那你为什么要这么做
Then what was the point?
哈维很烦躁
Harvey was upset.
他想平静下来
He needed to calm down--
通过被控制而得到一种控制感
to feel in control by being controlled.
他出钱让你这么做的吗
He pays you for this?
作为回报  他帮我上税  打扫房子
In return, he does my taxes and cleans my house.
我们还没结束  还没谈完呢
We're not done here. We have to talk.
报警吧
Call the cops.
把她关起来  叫她把你的乳头穿个孔
Bar her from the hospital. Force her to pierce your nipples.
开玩笑而已  不是真的医嘱
Not really medical decisions.
很久以前
It was a long time ago.
我和这种女人约会过  一个银行家
I was seeing this woman, a banker,
结果发现她喜欢被火烧
and, uh, turns out she liked to be burned.
你居然和一个喜欢被烧伤的人约过会
You actually dated someone who likes to get burned?
是啊  你为什么会喜欢上这种
Yeah, why would you want to be in a relationship...
明显只会带来痛苦的人
with someone that's so obviously only gonna lead to pain?
-住嘴  -这确实很奇怪
- Shut up. - It was a weird scene.
-我注意到  -奇斯
- I observed-- - Chase,
你认识这女人  她是干什么的
did you know about this woman, what she does?
我在某类"特殊聚会"上见过她
I met her at some parties, yeah.
要是早知道你喜欢"受虐"
I wouldn't have tortured you
我就不折磨你了
if I knew you liked it.
有句名言你要谨记
Well, here's a phrase to remember.
这家伙的脑袋也许
"Hey, this guy might have
已经被人揍过N多次了
been pounded on the head one too many times".
我说了  这是由外伤引起的动脉瘤
I said I thought it was a trauma-induced aneurysm.
是啊  要是你早说病人喜欢受虐
Yeah. Could have carried a tad more weight
你的意见就会有点分量了
if you'd mentioned the "Liking pain" Thing.
你上了我的捣蛋名单
You're on my naughty list.
抱歉  今年圣诞节不送你听诊器了
Sorry. No leather stethoscope this Christmas.
-我并非喜欢...  -我估计
- I'm not into--  - I assume you
你们还没给他用抗生素和血液稀释剂吧
never started him on antibiotics and blood thinners...
[伊莎夫人  《残酷疯淫所》主人公
代指施虐女王]
是不是都被伊莎夫人的疯狂举动吓到了
before Mistress Ilsa's rude interruption.
这也许是好事  因为...
That was probably a good thing, given--
给他上抗生素和血液稀释剂
Start him on antibiotics and blood thinners.
你还认为奇斯错了
You still think Chase is wrong?
不  他可能是对的
No, he's probably right.
那我们应该给他安排血管手术
Then we should schedule him for vascular surgery.
切开颈动脉  找到动脉瘤  然后切除
Go into the carotids, find the aneurysm, repair it.
如果用血液稀释剂  他可能会大出血
We put him on blood thinners, he might bleed out.
但是如果福曼的细菌性心内膜炎
But if Foreman's right about it
诊断是正确的  那我们
being bacterial endocarditis and we--
我觉得奇斯的诊断没错
I think Chase is right.
好吧  假如福曼之前的血栓理论是对的
Okay. If Foreman used to be right about it being blood clots...
而我们进行手术
and we take the surgery route,
那人估计就会被我们弄死了
we'll probably kill the guy.
所以  给他注射血液稀释剂
So start him on blood thinners,
如果他再次中风  我们就安排手术
and if he has another stroke, we'll schedule the surgery.
-什么事  -你是豪斯医生
- Yeah?  - You Dr. House?
我预感到我承认就会后悔
I have a feeling I'm gonna regret this,
不过  正是在下
but yes.
瑞蒙娜说我该来找你再开些药
Ramona said I should come to you for my refill.
呃  那个...
Uh, you know, the--
"小枝条"开始软软地下垂了
The wood's beginning to droop.
她说你可能会先跟我谈谈
She said you'd probably want to talk to me first.
她骗你呢
She lied.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
我一向助人为乐  再见
Always happy to make people happy. Good-bye.
我不知道我还能再坚持多久
Uh, I don't know how much more of this I can take.
-坚持什么  -做爱
- Much more of what? - Sex.
你不想再做爱了吗
You don't want more sex?
我都没力气打高尔夫了
My golf swing is all messed up.
最根本的解决方法  跟她谈谈
Hey, here's a radical thought. Talk to her.
-说实话吗  -实话实说很困难吗
- The truth? - Sounds crazy when you put it like that.
瑞蒙娜性欲旺盛啊
Ramona's got a big appetite.
如果我不做
If I don't perform--
我不想失去她
I don't want to lose her.
你这儿有药房吗
You got a pharmacy around here?
在医院吗  应该吧
In the hospital? Could be.
看看我们能不能找到
Let's see if we can find it.
有蓝色小药片吗
Got any blue pills?
你是找治疗勃起障碍的那种药吗
You looking for E.D. Medication?
那只是一种蓝色药片
Well, that's one example of a blue pill.
再另外说六个
Name six others.
有一种止痛片也是蓝色的
There's a brand of acetaminophen--
很好  把这装满
Perfect. Fill  her up.
豪斯医生
Dr. House.
正忙呢
Little busy here.
我听说了卡梅隆医生回来工作的条件
I heard about Dr. Cameron's conditions for coming back to work.
纯属公事  我会把小票给你的
It's purely business. I'll make sure you get the receipt.
我倒觉得这是个好事
Well, I think it's a good thing.
虽然你的上段感情惨淡收场
What happened in your last relationship,
但你不能永远拒人于千里之外
it's no reason to wall yourself off from people forever.
5年自怨自艾的生活也许足够了
Five years of self-pity is probably enough.
哇  您的话犹如醍醐灌顶啊
Wow. You've certainly given me a lot to think about.
如果我也能像你这么"开放"的话
If only I was as open as you.
其实我说的是你的衬衫
Actually, it was your blouse I was talking about.
记住
Bear in mind,
卡梅隆也许是唯一受得了你的女人
Cameron's probably the only female who could tolerate you.
穿那件天蓝的衬衫去
Wear the sky-blue shirt.
你穿那件很帅
It almost makes you look nice.
他们说她不能再到医院来
They said she couldn't come back into the hospital.
他们不让我见她
They won't let me see her.
哈维  她没被拘捕你就该庆幸了
Harvey, you're lucky she wasn't arrested.
在医院里这么干  你在想什么啊
What were you thinking, doing that at a hospital?
抓住我的手指
Squeeze my fingers?
我很害怕
I was scared.
你两只手都用力
I'll need you to squeeze with both hands.
我都使劲了呀
I am.
右臂和右手无力
Weakness in his right arm and hand.
哈维患了小中风
Harvey's having mini-strokes.
血液稀释剂没有起效
The blood thinners aren't making a difference.
停止治疗
Stop the treatment.
抱歉  你的方法我们试过了
Sorry. We tried your way.
你大错特错
You could not have been "Wronger".
-我说奇斯可能是对的  -是啊
- I said Chase was probably right.  - Oh, yeah.
马后炮谁都会放
We've all got perfect 20/20 hindsight.
尽快准备血管手术
Get ahold of may in Vascular.
看看明天主刀医生有没有空
See if his surgical dance card is free for tomorrow.
关于明天晚上
About tomorrow night.
你怎么这么大嘴巴
You couldn't keep your mouth shut.
没必要保密呀
I didn't see any reason to.
我们要去哪里  我想打扮的得体些
Where are we going? I want to make sure I dress appropriately.
穿个军靴和T恤好了
That would be army boots and T-shirt.
去参加彩蛋球比赛[军事模拟战]
It's the county paint ball tourney.
头奖50美金
First prize is 50 bucks.
如果你能坚持到底  奖金分你一半
I'll split it with you if you hold your end up.
我想我们当初不是这么说的吧
I'm not sure that was the deal.
放轻松  我已经在斯波莱托餐馆定了座
Relax. I made a reservation at Cafe Spoleto.
说到着装
Regarding wardrobe,
你是不是太小  没听说过氨纶
are you too young to remember spandex?
我还是自己解决吧
I'll figure something out.
手术会修复你颈部受损的血管
The surgery will repair the damaged blood vessels in your neck,
你就不会再中风了
and your strokes will stop.
这都是因为勒脖子引起的吗
All this is because of the strangulation?
很可能是
More like strangulations.
我父母说的没错
My parents are right.
我是个败类
I'm a loser.
我  我不知道
I don't -- I don't know what--
我不知道该干什么  我要
I don't know what to do. I need to--
哈维  冷静
Harvey, calm down.
我要和安妮特谈谈
I need to talk to Annette.
你自己能决定
You can do this on your own.
-手术只是...  -她恨我
- Surgery's the only-- - She hates me.
我一直打她电话  一直打
I've been calling. I've been calling and she--
她就是不接
She's not picking up.
哈维  你不需要
Harvey, you don't need--
我做不到  做不到
I can't. I can't.
哈维  照我说的做
Harvey, you will do what I say.
我不想做手术
I don't want surgery.
把同意书签了  签字
Sign the consent. Sign it!
我什么都做不了
I can't do anything.
不手术  不要手术
No surgery. No surgery!
我不做手术
No surgery!
给他用抗抑郁药
We could give him antidepressants.
看看他会不会改主意
See if he changes his mind.
已经试过了  我把药混在苹果汁里了
I already did. Mashed 'em up in his apple sauce.
应该很快就会见效的
It'll lighten him up soon enough.
最好有人能直接叫他同意手术
Someone should just tell him to do it.
这样快得多
Way faster.
伪造签名也很快  但这是违法的
So's forgery-- also illegal.
-我也试过了  -不是你
- And I already tried. - Not you.
当你渴望被虐的时候  上哪儿去找施虐狂
Where's a good dominatrix when you need one?
安妮特被禁止进入医院
Annette's barred from the hospital.
万一你也被抓
If you get caught,
我透露个小秘密给你  卡迪有把梳子
Cuddy's got a hairbrush,
并且那把梳子她还有别的"妙用"
and believe me, she knows how to use it.
他们让你回来了
They let you come back.
不是因为你表现好
Not because you deserve it.
你太不听话了
You've been bad.
你必须做这个手术  明白吗
You will have the surgery. Do you understand?
不
No.
别嬉皮笑脸的
Do not laugh at me.
你该尊敬我
You will respect me.
你算老几来  竟然来教我该怎么做
Where do you get off telling me what to do?
给我滚出去  你这个老巫婆
Get out of my room, you bag-faced witch.
他们平时也是这么对话的吗
Is this a part of their deal?
这不像他
This isn't like him.
-有点不对劲  -滚出去
- Something's wrong. - Get out!
出去  出去  滚出去
Get out! Get out! Get out!
出去
Get out!
情绪波动  他又中风了
Emotional swings-, he's having another stroke.
哈维
Harvey!
他不行了  这里需要急救推车
He's crashing. Can we get a cart in here?
怎么回事  你把这家伙吓得两次中风吗
So what's that? Two strokes you've scared this guy into?
没错
Yeah.
因此我开始怀疑自己与人交往的能力
It's making me question my view of myself as a people person.
现在你想不经过他同意就给他做手术吗
Now you want to do surgery on him without his consent?
那孩子已经昏迷了  他需要手术
The kid's in a coma. He needs the surgery.
他说了不做  我们不能做
He said no. We can't do it.
紧急情况  我们得特事特办
Emergent situation. We invoke heroic measures.
你需要一纸法院指令
You need a court order.
好啊  我要去哪弄
Great. Where do I get me one of them?
我要请个律师吗
Do I need to lawyer up?
我要向法官提供一份他直系亲属的同意书
I'll need to show the judge an affidavit from next of kin.
找他们签名可有点困难了
They might have a problem signing anything,
因为他们已经死了
seeing as how they're dead.
那要提供死亡证明
He'll want proof.
比如什么  他老爸的一只手吗
Like what, Dad's hand?
我连他们葬在哪里搜不知道
I don't even know where they're buried.
那给我一份讣告
Bring me a published obit,
或者是死亡证明  我去试试
or death certificate, and we'll run with it.
我可不想你连累我们
I don't want you to mess up your clothes.
他的父母都是会计
His parents were accountants.
也许金融类报纸上会有讣告
Maybe there's an obit in the trade papers.
他住在马克特镇
Guy lives in Market Town.
我不知道他是不是在那里长大
I don't know if he grew up there,
但我们可以去当地的殡仪馆查查
but we could check the local funeral homes.
很好  当你无功而返的时候
Great, and when your searches turn up nothing,
你就该去查查他们住在哪里
you should try and find where they live.
他说他们已经死了
He said they were dead.
会计可是高收入群体
Accountants are usually pretty good with money,
他怎么可能住在马克特那种贫民窟
so how come he lives in a slum like Market Town?
也许他们业务不精  收入低廉
Maybe they were bad accountants.
糟糕的亚洲会计会远渡重洋来到美国吗
Two bad accountants from the Pacific Rim?
简直是天方夜谭吧
The odds are astronomical.
也许哈维把钱挥霍一空了
Maybe Harvey burned through their money.
也许他们在发现他的特殊癖好后
Or maybe they cut him off
剥夺了他的继承权
when they found out about his proclivities.
我肯定没猜错  去他的公寓
Gotta be my bet. Go to his apartment.
看看能不能找到他的父母
See if you can find his folks.
号码  地址  等等
Number, address, something.
能跟你谈谈吗
Hey. Can I talk to you?
当然
Sure.
听着  卡梅隆是我们的朋友
Look. Cameron's a friend.
约会这事...
This whole dating--
时间到  感谢参与
Time's up. Thanks for playing.
说到约会  我可比你有经验的多
Hey, I've been on the scene more than you recently.
你差远了
Way ahead of you.
我准备了一箱麦芽酒
I got a case of malt liquor stashed in the trunk.
马文·盖耶[黑人歌手]的CD
Mr. Marvin Gaye on the CD.
我们会进展得很顺利  你可以走了
We are gonna get all the way down. Now move.
得了吧  你又不爱她
Come on. You're not into her.
大多数男人对某个女人没兴趣时
Most guys who aren't interested in a woman
都会表现得彬彬有礼
try to sugar coat it, be nice.
你真是太了解我了
Oh, you know me too well.
我就是这意思
That's what I'm saying.
我觉得你还是不要压抑自己的本性
I think you should go with your instincts here.
好好当个混蛋吧
Be a jerk.
我不看电视剧  就为了听你说这个
I'm missing my soap for this?
女人总希望自己是对的
Women love to be right.
你要让她们有种优越感
You gotta leave 'em feeling superior,
就像刚躲过一颗子弹
like they dodged a bullet.
但是如果你太和善  她会责怪自己
But if you're nice, she'll blame herself--
然后爱我更深
And fall for me even more.
爱情医生刚刚阐述了
The love doctor has made an art
和女人分手的艺术
out of breaking up with women...
因为你坚信
'cause you're convinced that
任何女人都无法承受你的离去
the loss of you would be too devastating for any woman to handle.
是啊  只有我如此自大
Yeah. I'm the one with the serious ego problem here.
我只想说
I'm just saying...
有些感情根本不应该开始
some relationships aren't meant to happen.
哈维的学校注册信息
Harvey's school registration.
有没有永久住址或紧急联系人
Permanent home address? Emergency contacts?
是安妮特·瑞恩斯
"Annette Rains".
安妮特情妇
Mistress Annette.
你要靠勒索才能跟豪斯约会
You had to extort a date out of House.
你不觉得这是个不好的预兆吗
You don't think that's a bad sign?
卡梅隆
Cameron?
高中年鉴
High school yearbook.
也许我们能在这发现线索  福尔摩斯
Think this might give us a clue, Sherlock?
豪斯不会主动给你什么
House isn't gonna hand you anything.
你要他  你就得主动出击
You want him, you gotta take him.
扑倒他
Jump him.
哈维  H-A-R-V-E-Y
Harvey-- H-A-R-V-E-Y.
很抱歉打扰你  谢谢
I'm sorry to have bothered you. Thank you. Okay.
对  哈维·帕克
Yes. Harvey Park.
太好了  我们找的就是你
Great. We've been looking for you.
我是普林斯顿普雷斯波罗教学医院的
I'm calling from the Princeton Plainsboro Teaching Hospital.
哈维在我们这里  他很...
Harvey's here, and it's rather--
他挂了
He hung up.
你跟他说了为什么要找他吗
You tell him why you were calling?
-还没来到及说呢  -打回去
- I didn't get a chance. - Call back.
我来打
I'll do it.
让师父教教你该怎么做
Let the master show you how it's done.
帕克先生吗  我是新泽西州
Mr. Park? This is Dr. House calling...
普林斯顿普波教学医院的豪斯医生
from Princeton Plainsboro Teaching Hospital in New Jersey.
你儿子哈维已经死了
Your son Harvey is dead.
我们需要你来认尸
We need you to identify the body.
是的  我很遗憾  法律规定
Yes. I'm sorry. It's the law.
好的
Okay.
这才是传达噩耗的艺术
There's a real art to delivering bad news.
他们会直接去太平间的
They're gonna show up at the morgue.
卡迪发飙的时候通知我
Be sure and let me know when Cuddy starts screaming.
你骗了他们
You lied to them!
他说我们的儿子死了
He told us our son was dead.
那只是善意的谎言
It's only a white lie.
准确地说  我只是提前通知他们而已
Technically, all I did was call them a little early.
相信我  他很快就要死了
Trust me. He'll be dead real soon.
实际上  我还替你们省了堵车的时间
Actually, I saved you some rush hour traffic.
我要打给我的律师
I'm calling our lawyer.
行  只要你签了手术同意书
Fine. Just as soon as you've signed the surgery consent.
我有笔
I have a pen.
我是玛丽莲·帕克  要找马克·莱纳
Marilyn Park for Mark Lerner.
好的  我等着
Yes, I'll hold.
哈维是你的儿子  我相信你还关心他
Harvey's your son. I'm sure you still care about him.
他令我们颜面尽失
He humiliated us.
所有人都知道他的...特殊癖好
Everybody we know knows about his... perversion.
但你面对困窘的方式跟你儿子不一样
But you don't get off on embarrassment the way your son does.
[embarrassment  双关
指困窘  也指呼吸困难]
我猜  这也许是隔代遗传吧
My guess, maybe it skips a generation.
你们要多少赔偿金
How much money would it take to compensate you--
你们可以等会再讨价还价  但问题是
Yeah, you guys can haggle in a minute, but here's the thing.
耻辱分很多种
Humiliation comes in all kinds of packages.
被人发现你儿子是性变态
People finding out that your son's a perv.
这确是一种奇耻大辱
That's pretty high up there.
但如果人们发现你坐视不理自己的儿子死去
People finding out that you'd rather let your son die...
也不愿签一纸文书
than sign a piece of paper--
哪个比较严重
Where's that rank?
相信我
Trust me,
必要时我会在宾州的每一家美甲店
if I have to paste up a sign... in every nail salon
和饺子店里贴上标语
and dumpling shop in Pennsylvania,
弄得人尽皆知
I'll make sure they know.
明天一早你们的儿子就会上手术台了
Your son will be in surgery first thing in the morning.
饺子店  这招够狠
Dumplings. That was a cheap shot.
嘿  你现在...
Hi. Are you, uh--
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
好啊  我倒想知道关于什么事
Gee, I wonder what this is gonna be about.
我只想确保没人会受伤
I just want to make sure no one gets hurt.
我会没事的
I will be fine.
你们让我觉得我像是要跟开膛手杰克去约会
Everybody's acting like I'm going out with Jack the Ripper.
不是  我担心的不是你
Oh. It's not-- It's not you I'm worried about.
他已经很久没有向别人敞开心扉  我
It's been a long time since he opened up to someone, and I--
你最好能肯定你确实想跟他在一起
You better be absolutely sure you want this,
因为如果他再一次敞开心扉而又受到伤害
because if he opens up again and gets hurt--
他可能永远也不会对他人敞开心扉了
I don't think there's gonna be a next time.
你担心我会伤他的心
You're worried I'm gonna break his heart?
宽的那端太短了
The wide side's too short.
活像娄·科斯特洛[喜剧演员]
You're gonna look like Lou Costello.
这就是个错误
This is a mistake.
我根本就不知道该怎样闲聊
I don't know how to have casual conversation.
你以为自己言之有物
You think you're talking about one thing,
可就算你没说废话  内容也无聊透顶
and either you are, and it's incredibly boring,
何况你根本就是想表达一些弦外之音
or you're not because there's a subtext,
还得多费唇舌解释才能明白
and you need a decoder ring.
为她开门  为她拉椅
Open doors for her. Help her with her chair.
我又不是没约会过
I have been on a date.
那已经是很多年前的事了
Not since disco died.
夸夸她的鞋子和耳坠
Comment on her shoes, her earrings,
然后开始谈D.H.A.
and then move on to D.H.A.
她的梦想  希望和抱负[首字母DHA]
Her dreams, hopes and aspirations.
相信我  就是这么简单【】
Trust me. Panty peeler.
需要套套的话我可以给你几个
And if you need condoms, I've got some.
你老婆给你的吗
Did your wife give them to you?
售药处给的
Drug rep.
他们在里面加了些抗体
They've got antibiotics built in somehow.
我该取消约会的
I should cancel.
我有个病人明早要做手术
I've got a patient in surgery tomorrow morning.
你又不是执刀医生
And if you were a surgeon,
有什么关系
that would actually matter.
不错的主意  缓解紧张
That's a good idea. Settle your nerves.
也给我来一瓶啤酒吧
Get me a beer too.
不是啤酒
No beer.
你在晚餐前还要吃东西吗
You're gonna eat before dinner?
这很逊  不是吗
This is pretty lame, right?
我觉得她喜欢这套
I think she likes lame.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
你看起来也很帅
And you look very handsome.
谢谢
Thank you.
我一直都挺喜欢这餐厅的
I've always loved this restaurant.
是啊  可现在变了不少
Yeah. It's changed a lot
跟我上次来这儿大有不同
since the last time I was here.
本来是个脱衣舞俱乐部的
Used to be a strip joint.
耳环不错
Nice earrings.
这是我妈妈的  谢谢
My mom's. Thank you.
鞋子也很好
Nice shoes.
穿着舒服吗
Comfortable?
我并没有期待你变成另一个人
I'm not expecting you to be someone you're not.
我们在餐馆里
We're in a restaurant.
正装出席  共进晚餐
We're dressed up. We're eating.
除了聊些鸡毛蒜皮的东西  还能干嘛
Without small talk, what is there?
根据弗洛伊德的学说  他大意如此
According to Freud-- and I'm paraphrasing--
人们对某物的爱
the instinct of love toward an object
是通过支配与占有而实现的
demands a mastery to obtain it,
如果他发现自己无法控制那东西
and if a person feels they can't control the object,
或感觉受到它的威胁
or feel threatened by it,
他们将会作出消极的回应
they act negatively toward it.
比如一个8年级男生去打一个小女生
Like an eighth-grade boy punching a girl.
我把你当成垃圾一样
I treat you like garbage,
所以我一定很喜欢你了
so I must really like you.
根据你的弗洛伊德理论
Given your Freudian theory,
要是我开始对你好又意味着什么
what does it mean if I start being nice to you?
你开始正视你的内心了
That you're getting in touch with your feelings.
所以我无论怎么做
So there's absolutely nothing I can do
你都会觉得我喜欢你
to make you think that I don't like you?
很抱歉  是的
Sorry, no.
我只此一次机会与你共度一晚  唯一的一次
I have one evening with you-- one chance--
我不想把时间浪费在讨论
and I don't want to waste it talking about
你喜欢什么葡萄酒或讨厌什么电影上
what wines you like or what movies you hate.
我想知道你的感觉
I want to know how you feel.
对我的感觉
About me.
你生活在错觉中
You live under the delusion
以为自己可以治愈一切不完美的东西
that you can fix everything that isn't perfect.
所以你嫁给一个
That's why you married a man
因癌症而垂死的男人
who was dying of cancer.
那不是爱  只是需要
You don't love, you need.
现在你丈夫去世了
And now that your husband is dead,
你又得找新的慈善对象
you're looking for your new charity case.
所以你才和我一起约会
That's why you're going out with me.
我年龄是你的两倍
I'm twice your age.
长得也不帅
I'm not great-looking.
还不迷人  甚至连脾气也很臭
I'm not charming. I'm not even nice.
你需要的就是这样的我
What I am is what you need.
支离破碎的我
I'm damaged.
你迟到了  昨晚进行得如何
Came in late. Good time last night?
手术情况如何
How's the surgery going?
哈维目前情况不错
Harvey's doing fine so far.
昨晚如何
How'd the night go?
非常好  你过得怎样
It was fine. How was your evening?
她点了意式馄饨  我点了凤尾鱼
She had the ravioli. I had the puttanesca.
是啊  接着说  你以为我要听你说食物呢
Yes, I really want to know about the quality of the food.
如果不是情况好极了
Either something very good
就是彻底搞砸了  是哪种情况
happened or something very bad. Which is it?
好吧  吃完饭我的确有点消化不良
Well, I did have a little indigestion afterwards.
可能是因为那个蒜蓉包
Maybe it was the garlic bread.
要不然就是葡萄酒  让我眼睛有些浮肿
Or the wine. Something made my eyes puffy.
恐怕是因为捂着枕头哭吧
Crying in your pillow can do that.
绝对是因为葡萄酒
It was the wine.
我们聊天聊得很愉快
We had a nice candid conversation.
没什么深入话题  就是在闲聊
Nothing deep. Mostly small talk.
我就知道
I'm sure.
照你说的那样  赞美了她的鞋子
Took your advice. Complimented her shoes.
就这个整整聊了15分钟
That's 15 minutes of chat right there.
尖酸刻薄的评论呢
No snide comments?
我觉得在聊到你们的时候是有一些
I guess-- when we talked about you guys.
一句话说
Just answer one question.
你们会再约会吗
You two gonna do dinner again?
我觉...得应该不会了
I... don't think so.
我...不知道
I... don't know.
孩子们  你们错了
Hey, kids. You were wrong.
没有动脉瘤  什么也没有
No aneurysm, no nothin'.
这家伙什么都没长
This guy's clean.
意味着我们完全不知道中风的原因
Which means we've got no idea what's causing the strokes.
手术后他又发作了两次
He's had two more post-op.
要等到他清醒过来我们才能知道
We won't know the extent of the damage...
损伤有多严重
until he comes out of the coma--
如果他能醒过来的话
if he comes out.
可能我们该重新用血液稀释剂
Maybe we should go back to the blood thinners.
加大剂量
Up the dosage.
如果不是血栓  过量的稀释剂
If it's not clots, a loading dose of blood thinners
会让他耳出血
is gonna make him bleed out of his ears.
这样他就聋了
Then he won't be able to hear.
没人在家  留言吧
Nobody home. Leave a message.
这很重要
This is important.
奇斯和卡梅隆  重做血管造影和超声波
Chase, Cameron, get another angiogram and echo.
做个全身扫描
You better get a full body scan.
如果真是血栓   最好确定它们的位置
If it is clots, it'd be good to know where they are.
非常抱歉
Sorry about that.
有病人快死了
Guy dying.
你给玛艾隆的药根本没用
Those pills you gave Myron? They're not working.
好吧  真高兴你们对这件事
Well, good to see you've got
有了个正确的认知
the correct perspective on the thing.
以前的药物让我感觉像树一样坚挺
Well, the old ones, I mean, made me feel like a tree, you know?
好比喻
Nice visual.
但是新的药物
But the new ones,
就跟吃糖豆差不多
I might as well be eating candy.
-糖豆可治不了你的头痛  -什么
- Candy wouldn't take away your headaches. - What?
你来找我
You came to me and told me
抱怨你们性生活太多
you were having too much sex.
-我没有  -你也一样  "大树"
-I never did.  -You too, sequoia.
那不是真的 我
Well, no, that's not true. I--
我知道谁都会说谎
I know everybody lies,
但你们共同生活了这么久
but you'd think that after a certain amount of time together,
不会还这么激情燃烧的
you wouldn't be trying so hard.
你们的婚戒不一样
Your rings don't match.
为什么要一模一样
Why would they?
风格是一回事
The style is one thing,
但一个银的一个金的就不对劲了
but one silver, one gold?
你们结婚多久了
How long have you guys been married?
-55年  -49年
-Fifty-five years.  -Forty-nine years.
该死  你们在搞外遇
Damn it. You're having an affair.
你真的说过你想少做点爱吗
Did you really say you wanted to have less sex?
只是少一点而已  要是我不想做
Well, less. If I wanted none,
我就会待在家里陪依斯瑟了
I'd stay home with Esther.
我只是需要休息一下
I just need a little rest.
你们俩不是蓝色小药丸的受害者
You guys aren't the victims of the little blue pills,
问题在于你们本身
you're the problem.
-我很抱歉  -我也是
-I'm sorry. -Me too.
我该告诉你我的感受的
I should just have told you how I felt.
欢迎来到地狱
Oh, welcome to hell.
药怎么办
Uh, hey, how about the pills?
看起来你们最好过几天没药的日子
Looks like you guys are good to go drug-free for a while.
奇斯医生  从昨天起
Dr. Chase, these breath mints
你就开始一个劲在吃薄荷糖
you've been popping since yesterday--
你迷恋上这玩意儿了吗
are they a new fetish?
我在哈维家找到的
I found them at Harvey's.
怎么了  我只拿了两盒
What? I just took two boxes.
那家伙有一整抽屉呢
The guy's got a whole drawer of them.
而你甚至不觉得这有趣吗
And you didn't find that interesting?
好吧  他那儿"有趣的东西"太多了
Well, there's lots of interesting stuff in his place.
薄荷糖实在不怎么起眼
The mints weren't high up on the list.
大错特错
Wrong.
奇斯  把鼻子伸过来
Chase, get your nose in here.
如果你是想让我难堪
If you're trying to humiliate me,
我告诉你
I told you--
来吧  伸鼻子
Come on. Put your face in his mouth.
挺浓郁的不是吗
Rich, wouldn't you say?
闻起来像放久了的呕吐物
Smells like old vomit.
爆发性骨髓炎的显要特征
Number one sign of fulminating osteomyelitis.
下巴感染吗
Infection of the jaw?
很可能是旧伤引起的
Probably from the original break.
从未被治愈
Never healed properly.
下巴的感染组织
Infected tissue from the jaw...
脱落下来  堵塞通向脑部的血流
breaks off, blocks blood flow to the brain.
没有血液  生命还如何维系正常
And life just isn't worth living without blood.
金属盘使它无法显示在扫描中
It was hidden from the scans by the metal plate.
而下巴部位的感染
And an infection in the jaw
也不太可能在血液中表现出来
is unlikely to show up in blood tests.
-那我们要怎么确认  -像这样
-So how do we confirm? -Like this.
女士们先生们  脓液
Ladies and gentlemen, we have pus.
我们要移除下巴
We're gonna remove the jaw.
你们谁有电锯吗  叫个外科医生吧
Anybody got a buzz saw? Okay, call a surgeon.
我是豪斯医生
Hi. I'm Dr. House.
易装的感觉如何啊  安妮特
How's tricks, Annette?
我只想看看他是否还好
I just wanted to see if he was okay.
我这就走
I'll leave.
没事  我是来跟你俩说话的
It's okay. I came to talk to you both.
像我对所有病人建议的那样
Like I tell all my patients,
你们最好停止窒息行为
you've simply got to say no to strangulation.
我自己是个怪胎
Me, I'm a freak.
没有疼痛我反而无法工作
I get off on not being in pain.
对了  还有巧克力糖衣的棉花糖
That and chocolate-covered marshmallow bunny.
他不是怪胎
He's not a freak.
他是  有点怪
Yeah, he is... A little.
但这必须停止
But it's gotta stop,
要不然他就会死
or he'll die.
这与疼痛无关
It's not about pain.
而是将自己的生命交到别人手上
It's about being open.
对那个人毫不设防
And completely vulnerable to another person.
如果你能懂得如此深刻的信任
If you can learn to be that deeply trusting,
这将改变你
it changes you.
把他锁在笼子里
Lock him in a cage.
这在医学上说没什么大碍
That should be fine, medically.
豪斯先生
Dr. House?
我父母来过医院吗
Were my parents here?
他们来看我了吗
Did they come to see me?